Ben

Davis

Contact

Address:

Kievska, Ternopil, Ukraine

Email:

topdev900502@outlook.com

Skype:

live:.cid.e07bcb612fe88d1b

Language:

English - C1

Skills:

React

React Native

Vue

Javascript

Typescript

HTML

CSS

SASS

Bootstrap

Node.js

Express.js

Laravel

MongoDB

MySQL

Summary

I have a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and have been a **full-stack developer** since 2013. I have worked on 20+ projects and solved complex business problems with MERN & MEAN stacks in various industries including marketing, healthcare and eCommerce. I have consistently saved costs while increasing profits.

Skill Highlights

- User familiar UI/UX design
- Database Architecture
- RESTful API
- Soket IO
- Good communication

Experience

Senior Full Stack Developer - 06/2019 to 07/2021 ITECHART GROUP, New York, United States

- Created a cross-platform full-featured comment editor based on the one on Facebook.com.
- Use Node.js, PostgreSQL, and Ruby on Rails to develop back-end features to support the front-end.
- Implement fully responsive pixel-perfect cross-platform designs in React and SASS.
- Delivered multiple hybrid multi-platform mobile apps as a solo developer that connected to custom made APIs.

Full Stack Developer - 05/2016 to 07/2019 ANDERSEN INC, New York, United States

- Constructed a Chrome developer tool to help developers debug and analyze a proprietary state-management framework.
- Constructed middleware that allowed React to work with our proprietary model framework.
- Developed friendly Ruby on Rails APIs for our front-end application.

Education

Bachelor of Degree in **Computer Science** - 2013 **University of Toronto**,

Toronto, Canada 2008 - 2012

Certification

Certified Web and Mobile Application Developer

Provider: SMTP Issued: January 2020